准备好了吗  孩子们
Are you ready, kids?
好了船长
Aye aye, captain
我听不见
I can't hear you
好了船长
Aye aye, captain
是谁住在深海的大菠萝里
Who lives in a pineapple under the sea?
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob SquarePants
方方黄黄伸缩自如
Absorbent and yellow and porous is he
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob SquarePants
如果四处探险是你的愿望
If nautical nonsense be something you wish
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob SquarePants
那就敲敲甲板让大鱼开路
Then drop on the deck and flop like a fish
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob SquarePants
准备
Ready
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob SquarePants
夹娃娃机
分镜总监
编剧
翻译: 1440kHz
技术总监
动画总监
制片指导
本字幕仅限学习交流
严禁用于商业用途
蟹堡王
蟹老板  有个西装革履的
Mr. Krabs, some guy in a suit
想在开门前进来
wants to come in before we open
什么
What?
此处点餐
有个西装革履的
Guy in a suit?
不好了
No
收税的来了
It's a tax collector
隐蔽好  海绵宝宝
Hide us, SpongeBob
快假装没事  走后门溜出去
Now we'll walk nonchalantly to the rear exit
他有张名片
He's got a card
RA小气鬼  贩卖机公司
"R.A. PennyPincher Vending Supplies"
什么
What?
我的机器到了
My machine has arrived?
放进来
Let him in
把它带进来
Bring it in, boys
没错  慢慢放好
That's it, set her down easy
钥匙给你  蟹老板
Here are the keys, Mr. Krabs
贩卖愉快
Happy vending
这什么东西
What is it?
有蟹黄堡以来最伟大的摇钱树
Only the greatest moneymaker since the Krabby Patty
各位  这个是夹娃娃机
Gentlemen, meet "Skill Crane"
夹娃娃机
Skill Crane
一次只要两毛五
At a quarter a pop
马上就能回本
this thing will pay for itself in no time
这倒让我想起来了
Which reminds me--
过来试试吧
step up, boys
第一次免费
First one's free
谢了  蟹老板
Thanks, Mr. Krabs
我还是免了
No, thanks, I'll pass
章鱼哥  你肯定会想来一手
Come on, Squidward, you know you want to
好吧
Okay
要我来我就来
If you insist
谢了
Thanks
章鱼哥
Squidward
去玩机器
In the machine
好吧好吧
All right, all right
天啊  真好玩
Oh, boy, what fun
你输了
You lose
看见没  海绵宝宝
Did you see that, SpongeBob?
我第一次差点就夹到了
I almost got that on my first try
我的活儿完成了
My work here is done
我这外号
They don't call me
章鱼哥灵巧手操大师  可不是白叫的
"Squidward Manual- Dexterity-Tentacles" for nothing
那我试试看好了
Well, why don't I give it a try?
祝你好运
Good luck
你不可能
You'll never
赢了
Winner
是只小熊
It's a bear
我要叫你熊熊
I'm going to call you Beary
新手运气好而已
Beginner's luck
到大佬玩了
Now it's the master's turn
抓
输了
Loser
章鱼哥  你把娃娃翻过来了
Squidward, you flipped him over
得要不少技巧才做得到
That takes an awful amount of skill
谢谢你这么说
Well, thank you for saying so
熊熊说自己有点寂寞
Beary says he's getting lonely
放心  熊熊
Don't worry, Beary
这就给你夹个朋友
I'll get you a friend
你要是以为能再赢一次
If you think you're going to win that thing again
赢了
Winner
你赢了
朋友给你吧  熊熊
There you go, Beary
我那是帮你舒展了一下机器
I loosened that one up for you
没我的技术  你绝对赢不了
You would have never won that without my skill
多谢你帮忙  章鱼哥
Thanks for your help, Squidward
我下次玩一定会赢
I bet I win at this thing the very next time I try
只要我
Now, all I've got to do is
一次只要两毛五
At a quarter a pop
马上就能回本
this thing pays for itself in no time
我才不会信那种废话
I'm not falling for that malarkey
章鱼哥
Hey, Squidward
好了  摇摆太太
Okay, Mrs. Wiggles--
上菜了
order up
熊熊自个儿做的蟹黄堡
Beary cooked this one all by himself
他让我好骄傲
He makes me so proud
章鱼哥
Squid-ward?
怎么
What the?
来把这夹娃娃机解决了
All right, let's get this over with
要不要零钱
Need change?
给你吧
There you are
多谢你了
Gee, thanks
不用了  章鱼哥先生
No, no, Mr. Squidward
谢你才对
Thank you
你输了
You lose
还要零钱吗
Need some more change?
你输了
You lose
要零钱吗
Need some change?
不要
No
为  为什么
W-Why?
因为我已经完全没有
Because I'm all out of
钱了
money
完全没有
All out of
各位  今天发工资
Boys, it's payday
可是蟹老板  今天才星期一
But Mr. Krabs, today is Monday
不对
No
今天就是要发工资
it's payday, me boy
工资单拿去  海绵宝宝
Here's your check, SpongeBob
钱  钱
Money, money
我冒昧把你的工资换成了零钱
I took the liberty
of turning your paycheck into quarters
以防你想要
just in case you want to
怎么说呢
I don't know
洗衣服或者买汽水
do laundry or buy a soda
或者
or
什么的
something
真幽默  蟹老板
Very funny, Mr. Krabs
我要是拿这两毛五还赢不到那些破烂
If I can't win one of those
stupid things with this quarter
马上就走
I'm walking away
六小时后
不好意思  章鱼哥
Pardon me, Squidward
这位海绵小熊熊
SpongeBear Junior here
想要我帮他赢个弟弟
wants me to win him a little brother
你赢了
You are a winner
才花两毛五就抓了俩
Two in one quarter?
太不公平了
That's not fair
说什么  皱眉小丑
What's that, Clown Frown?
你比较想坐可爱狮旁边吗
You'd rather sit next to Lovely Lion?
安顿好了  舒舒服服
There you are, nice and cozy
再见了  章鱼哥
See you later, Squidward
看点无脑的电视
A little mind-numbing television
应该就能让我忘掉那破机器了
ought to help me forget about that stupid machine
今天过得太不顺了  章鱼哥
You've had a rough day, Squiddy
不过也不代表明天不会好起来
but that doesn't mean tomorrow won't be better
烦死了
Phooey
我一定要夹到娃娃
I got to win that crane
就一次
Just once
拜托  拜托啊
Please, oh, please
就让我赢一次吧
let me win one time
章鱼哥  你好像有问题
Squid, I think you have a problem
他才没有呢
No, he doesn't
别听他的  章鱼哥
You don't listen to him, Squidward
继续玩下去  不赢不罢休
you keep playing until you win
这是什么
What's this?
我房子的地契
The deed to my house
那好吧
Okey-dokey, then
继续
Carry on
能赢一次我就不玩了
If I could just win once, I'd never play again
你要我告诉你秘诀
You want me to tell you the secret
帮你成功夹到娃娃吗
of how to win on this machine?
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob--
居然有秘诀吗
there's a secret?
快告诉我
Tell me
秘
the
诀
secret
你准备好要赢了吗
Are you ready to be a winner?
好了
Yes
好没
Yeah?
好了
Yeah
好没
Yes?
好了
Yes
好没
Yeah?
好了
Yeah
好没
Yes?
海绵宝宝  说秘诀
SpongeBob, the secret
好吧好吧  章鱼哥
Okay, Squidward, okay
面对夹娃娃机  投入硬币
I face the crane, deposit my quarter
然后闭上双眼
then I close my eyes
闭上双眼
Close your eyes?
别吵  章鱼哥
Quiet, Squidward--
我在与机器合二为一
I'm being the crane
纯属扯淡
That's ludi
赢了
Winner
看吧
See?
换你试试
Now you try
太离谱了
This is ridiculous
都闭眼了咋知道哪里
If I close my eyes, how will I know where
章鱼哥  你到底想不想赢了
Squidward, do you want to win or not?
想
Yes
我想赢
Yes, I do
好吧
Okay
章鱼哥  投币吧
Squidward, put your quarter in
可这是我最后的两毛五了
But this is my last quarter
投入机器  章鱼哥
In the machine, Squidward
好好好
Okay, okay
闭上双眼
Close your eyes
与机器合二为一
Now be the crane
合二为一
Be the crane
赢了
Winner
好耶
Yeah
我就知道我能行
I knew I could do it
我赢了
I'm a winner
你赢了
You're a winner
我是大赢家  对吧
I am a winner, aren't I?
赢了赢了赢了
Winner, winner, winner
赢了
Winner
大家看我  我赢了
I'm a winner, everybody
听见没
You hear that?
我是
I'm
大赢家
a winner
有点意思  据我所知
That's funny, last time I checked
你就只是个收银员
you were a cashier
随你怎么笑  蟹老板
Yuck it up all you want, Mr. Krabs
但是别忘了
but just remember
你这可是在大赢家面前笑
You're yucking in the presence of a winner
我尽量不忘
I'll try to remember that
章鱼哥第3498个两毛五
3,498 of Squidward's quarters
章鱼哥第3499个两毛五
3,499 of Squidward's quarters
三层堡上菜了
Triple-decker on deck
别挡大赢家的路
Make way for the winner
你输了
You lose
你没赢到奖吗
You didn't win the prize?
对
No
知道什么意思吗
You know what that means?
不知道
No
啥意思
What?
意思就是
It means
你没技术  注定要输
you have no skills and you're a loser
我赢了  看我赢的奖
I'm a winner, see my prize
你就一输家  就只会坐着哭
You're a loser who sits and cries
你看见我刚刚怎么夹娃娃的吗
Did you see how I handled that crane?
看见了
I sure did
我好像是身怀绝技
I think I have the magic touch
我就直接闭上双眼
I just closed my eyes
与机器合二为一
and became the crane
没错  你厉害
Oh, yeah, you're the man
海绵宝宝  你看
SpongeBob, look
章鱼哥  此夹非彼夹吧
Squidward, I don't think the same principles apply
与机器合二为一
Be the crane
等等  章鱼哥
Wait, Squidward
与机器合二为一
Be the crane
他做到了
He did it
章鱼哥
Squidward
合二为一  合二为一
Be the crane, be the crane
合二为一
Be the crane
你认识那位吗
You know this guy?
认识啊  那是章鱼哥
Yeah, that's Squidward
而且身怀绝技
He's got the magic touch
你的新商场
哒哒
Ta-dah
章鱼哥  睁开双眼
Squidward, open your eyes
合二为一  合二为一
Be the crane, be the crane
小心  海绵宝宝
Look out, SpongeBob
我停不下来了
I can't stop
合二为一  合二为一
Be the crane, be the crane
好
Okay
别合二为一  别合二为一
don't be the crane, don't be the crane
怎么
What the?
天啊  天啊
Oh, my, oh, my
该走了  泰迪
Time to go, Teddy
你这是想去哪呢  乱夹大师
Just where do you think you're going, crane master?
哪都不准去
You ain't going anywhere
坚持住  兄弟
Hang on, buddy
我来救你了
I got you
貌似我只会夹娃娃
I guess I can only pick up toys
好邻居
分镜总监
编剧
翻译: 1440kHz
技术总监
动画总监
制片指导
本字幕仅限学习交流
严禁用于商业用途
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob
早安  章鱼哥
Good morning, Squidward
海绵宝宝  你来我家干什么
SpongeBob, what are you doing in my house?
来确保你没睡过头
I came to make sure you don't oversleep
进而误工
and miss work
海绵宝宝啊
Oh, gee, SpongeBob
你可真贴心啊
that's very thoughtful of you
不客气  章鱼哥
My pleasure, Squidward
好邻居就该互帮互助
That's what good neighbors are for
不过你忽略了个小小的小细节
You did overlook one teensy, little detail, however
什么细节  章鱼哥
What's that, Squidward?
今天星期天
It's Sunday
好邻居不会在星期天打扰我
A good neighbor doesn't bother me on Sunday
星期天
Sunday
怪不得章鱼哥这么暴躁
No wonder Squidward's grumpy
周日的报纸他忘了拿
He forgot his Sunday papers
就用这个向章鱼哥证明我是好邻居
This will show Squidward I'm a good neighbor
把报纸带给他
I'll bring it to him
也太重了吧
Man, this is heavy
不好意思
Pardon me
走路看路
Watch where you're going
报纸怪
A newspaper monster
有怪物
Monster
你们俩白痴能不能行行好别吵了
Will you two nincompoops kindly quiet down?
绝对不能让他们
I am not going to let them
毁了我星期天剩下的时光
ruin the rest of my Sunday
我的星期天放松装备
My Sunday relaxation kit
星期天
来看看  枕头
Let's see, pillow
这么放好  稍微垫垫脚
placed just so for slight foot elevation
鲜花  用来点缀房间
flower to brighten the room
花香
flower fragrance
还有最后一步
And the final touch
没错  我想点星期天特别服务
Yes, I'd like to order the Sunday special
没错  上门修脚足部按摩
Yes, the pedicure-and-foot-massage house call
就是这样
that is correct
四点见  好先生
See you at 4:00, my good man
今天一定特别美好
This is going to be a heavenly day
差点忘了
I almost forgot
夹心糖
Bon-bon
你好啊  天堂来的小奇迹
Hello there, heaven's little wonder
带我度个巧克力假
Take me on a chocolate vacation
全视之眼在上
By the all-seeing eye
你值得敬重  而我们不配
ye are worthy, we are not
你们俩白痴在干什么
What are you two idiots doing?
秘密仪式
Secret ritual
为你举行主席就任典礼
To inaugurate you as president
我
Me?
裤头村主席
President of Bikini Bottom?
大众总算是觉醒了
I knew the people would come to their senses
不对  笨蛋
No, silly--
才不是裤头村的主席
not the president of Bikini Bottom
比那更厉害呢
Even better
更厉害
Better?
你是好邻居皇家密令共济会主席
You're the president of
the Secret Royal Order of the Good Neighbor Lodge
什么
The what?
这是又胡编乱造了个什么破会吗
Is this some stupid club you two made up?
有可能
Maybe
这可是秘密
It's a secret
好
Fine
我要颁布第一道主席令
As my first presidential decree, uh
让你们
why don't you, uh
出去把树叶都粉刷一遍
go out and paint all the leaves on the trees
美化附近的街区
to make the neighborhood look nicer
快出去出去出去
Now, out, out, out, out, out
这下他们好几个星期天都有得忙了
That'll keep 'em busy for a few Sundays
要把树叶粉刷成什么颜色  主席大人
What color should we
paint the leaves, Your Presidentialocity?
刷成斑点
Polka dots
别再来烦我了
Now, don't bother me anymore
斑点
Polka dots
新主席可真天才
Our new president is a genius
对啊
Yeah
再见  章鱼哥
See you later, Squidward
准备好就动手吧  派大星
Whenever you're ready, Patrick
不要动  兄弟
Hold still, buddy
派大星  快点晃我
Okay, Pat, give me a quick shake
没问题
Okey-dokey
行了  我准备好了
Okay, I'm ready
完美奏效了
That worked perfectly
来吧  好邻居派大星
Come on, good neighbor Patrick
一起把整个裤头村都刷成斑点吧
Let's paint the town polka-dot
不好了  已经中午了
Oh, no, it's already noon
不能让那几个白痴
I will be darned if I let those morons
再浪费我宝贵的星期天时光
eat up any more of my valuable Sunday
我们就是好邻居
Good neighbors are we
外面是怎么了
What's going on out there?
章鱼哥主席好
Hi, President Squidward
就快粉刷完了
Almost done painting
我的眼睛
My eyes
小心
Look out
你真可怜
You poor man
一定病得不轻
You must be very sick
我们送你去医院吧
Let us take you to the hospital
真不用
No, really
我没事  行行好
I'm fine, please
没有
No
我没事
I'm fine
再见了  邻居
See you later, neighbor
今天天气好  适合到乡下兜风
It is a lovely day for a ride in the country
对啊
Yeah
我们的主席太懂生活了
Our president sure knows how to live
好邻居
共济会
我宣布
I would like to call
本次好邻居共济会大会现在开始
this meeting of the Good Neighbor Lodge to order
首先开始点名
Let's begin with roll call
派大星
Patrick
好
Okay
章鱼哥
Squidward?
章鱼哥  你在家吗
Squidward, you home?
找到他了吗  海绵宝宝
Did you find him, SpongeBob?
没
Nope
多半还在兜风享受星期天
I guess he's still on his Sunday drive
也有可能是在执行秘密任务
Or maybe he's on a secret mission
希望他没危险
I hope he's not in danger
危险
Danger?
我们身为好邻居共济会成员
As members of the Good Neighbor Lodge
宣誓要保护主席免受危险
we are sworn to protect our president from danger
不好意思
Excuse me
有谁订购了上门修脚足部按摩
Somebody ordered
a relaxing pedicure and foot massage
星期天特别服务
the Sunday special
派大星会友  最好检查一下这位
Brother Star, we better check this guy out
保证他不会危害到章鱼哥
make sure he's safe for Squidward
起码我还有
At least I still have
日思夜想的星期天修脚服务
my Sunday pedicure to look forward to
你们两个在我家干什么
What are you two doing in my house?
我们在做检查  要确保这位
We're checking to make sure this guy
真的是个专业修脚师傅
really is a certified foot masseur
不是什么刺客
and not some kind of assassin
他检查通过了
Well, I say he checks out a-okay
章鱼哥  我可爱的法式甲片你见过没
Squidward, have you ever seen more lovely French tips?
法式甲片是吧
French tips, huh?
我说你呢
All right, pal
马上给我来个足部放松按摩
make with a relaxing foot massage, pronto
抱歉  服务时间结束了
Sorry, your hour's up
你们两个  滚出去
All right, you two, out
休想再来这里犯傻捣乱
Don't even think about
dragging your empty skulls around here
后半天也别来
for the rest of the day
明天也是  下周也是
or tomorrow or next week
章鱼哥  那算不算
Squidward, does that include
当然算
Yes, it does
派大星  你觉得
Gee, Patrick, do you think
章鱼哥是不是话里有话
Squidward was trying to tell us something?
我还真有
Yes, I was
你们管自己叫好邻居是吗
You call yourselves good neighbors?
你们纯粹就是最差邻居
You're the worst neighbors ever
不配戴着红圆帽
You don't deserve to wear those fezzes
派大星  可能真让章鱼哥主席说中了
Gee, Pat, maybe President Squidward's right
确实
Yeah
到头来我们并不是好邻居
I guess we aren't good neighbors after all
本来就不是
No, you aren't
你们就是烂邻居
You're horrible neighbors
不准再叫我主席
And stop calling me president
我们走吧
Come on, let's go
我的星期天只剩三小时了
There are only three hours of my Sunday left
全让他们浪费了
They took it all away
连周日的报纸都没来得及看
I didn't even get to read the Sunday paper
这是你的周日报纸  章鱼哥
慢慢看吧  爱你的海绵宝宝
好邻居  我的权利
Good neighbors, my right
哎呀
Hello
永远拦住入侵者
全新安保系统5000
免费安装
系统已启动
System activated
这样应该就行了
Well, that ought to do it
开
倒要看看那几个傻子还怎么进来
Let's see those imbeciles try to get in here now
章鱼哥主席
President Squidward?
怎么
What the
我们特此献上这个美味蛋糕
We hereby present you with this delicious cake
抱歉老是烦你
章鱼哥
怎么
What the
安保系统  救命
Security system, help
入侵者警报  入侵者警报
Intruder alert, intruder alert
开
你怎么回事
What's the matter with you?
未检测到威胁
你这破铜烂铁
You infernal contraption
非把你送回制造你的垃圾堆不可
I'll ship you off to the scrap heap you came from
未检测到威胁
检测到威胁
怎么回事
What's going on?
检测到威胁
红色警报
好像个嘉年华游乐设施
It's like a carnival ride
快逃命啊
Run for your lives
怎么
What the
你在干什么
What are you doing?
就只剩下半小时可以独处了
I only have half an hour of me-time left
结果我家被那俩白痴占了
and the idiots took my house
这就表示那俩笨蛋不会来烦我了
Which means those boobs aren't around to bug me
就等着这一刻呢
Just what I've been waiting for
就算拼了老命  我都要放松
I am going to relax, if it kills me
开火
Fire
章鱼哥家在破坏附近的街区
Squidward's house is destroying the neighborhood
一定要把这东西关了
We got to turn this thing off
不是这个
Nope, not it
不对
Nope
这个也不是
That's not it, either
在星期天放松正合我意
This Sunday relaxation really hits the spot
要找哪才对呢
Where to look?
关闭按钮
这个关闭按钮看着挺可疑
This "off" button seems suspicious
成功关掉了  派大星
We did it, Patrick
章鱼哥主席
President Squidward
别  别
No, no
什么都别再说了
Don't say anything more
全都要怪我
This was all my fault
都怪我想在星期天休息
I was the one who wanted to relax on Sunday
麻烦你们出去
Now, if you'll be so kind as to leave
好让我准备明天上班
so I can get ready for work tomorrow
主席大人
Mr. President
闭嘴
Shush
可我们只是想
But we just wanted to
滚出我家
Get out of my house
他在那
There he is
你是屋主吗
Are you the owner of this house?
没错
Yes
我就是
Yes, I am
那么我代表裤头村全体居民
Then on behalf of the citizens of Bikini Bottom
给你送上这张传票
I present you with this summons
要求赔偿你对裤头村造成的损失
to pay for the destruction of our town
你下半辈子每星期天都要做社区服务
You'll be doing community service
every Sunday for the rest of your life
章鱼哥  你也收到了吗
Squidward, you got one of those, too?
这也太棒了吧
This will be great--
我们三个一起清理裤头村
the three of us cleaning up Bikini Bottom
下周星期天再见  章鱼哥主席
Well, see you next Sunday, President Squidward